

Maykon Willian Rodrigues da SIlva

Developer

Profile

Fascinated by electronics since I was young, my journey as a programmer began at 17 years old. Using React, Typescript, and GraphQL, I explored projects for fun and learning. In 2020, I committed to programming, moving from an internship to junior developer. With a desire to continue learning, I constantly seek new technologies for professional and personal growth.

Employment History

Junior Developer at ACCT Global by Quality, São Paulo

June 2022 — December 2023

- Develop e-commerce applications, customizations and new features using technologies: Javascript, React, Gatsby, Nextjs, Typescript, jquery, VTEX IO, VTEX CMS, Jamstack and GraphQL.
- Support the squad by clarifying technical doubts to achieve the sprint objectives.
- Define technical solutions for e-commerce customizations and new features requested by customers.
- · Conduct code review of teammates.
- Carry out version releases.
- Deploy new features and fixes in a productive environment.

Development Intern at ACCT Global by Quality, São Paulo

January 2021 — June 2022

Education

Systems Analysis and Development, Univille

August 2020 — August 2024

Courses

VTEX IO Developer, VTEX

December 2022 — December 2024

Cloud Foundations, AWS Academy

August 2021 — Present

Details

Brasil

(47) 98856-0032

maykonsilva60@gmail.com

Skills

React

TypeScript

JavaScript

JQuery

GraphQL

Bootstrap

Node.js

Git

Code Review

SQL

CSS

HTML

MySQL

Languages

Portuguese

English